"Because... I want to be more than just friends."
"And the winning team is..."
"Team B... Mr. Pong."
"Last time... you just got lucky."
"But truth be told... someone like you could never beat me."
"I bet Pong sent someone to steal our prototype."
"I've done everything Dad told me to..."
"I gave the designs to Pong..."
"Are you satisfied now, Dad?"
"How are you... feeling any better?"
"Otherwise, I really don't know how else to cheer you up."
"Aargh!! Din!"
"I'm really sorry."
"Din..."
"Oh... hey."
"How are you holding up?"
"Got ten stitches."
"The doctor did a really great job, you know."
"I'll go handle your medical bill."
"What are you doing?"
"Just sit down. I'll handle this."
"Don't feel bad about it."
"I want to make it up to you."
"And how will you do that?"
"Like this... I'll go pay for your bill."
"I told you, you don't have to."
"Please... just let me help."
"Please... I'll feel so guilty if I don't."
"I don't want to feel guilty forever."
[ CASHIER ]
"Please... I already feel bad enough as it is."
"I'm the reason you got hurt. Just let me help."
"Come on!
Go sit down."
"Yaa... I told you, you don't have to."
"Din... please. Otherwise, I'll definitely feel guilty forever."
"Company insurance covers it..
You don't have to pay today."
"Oh... right, insurance."
"I didn't even think of that."
"Our company's pretty awesome, huh?"
"Mmm... but I still feel guilty anyway, Sorry."
"Stop it... It was an accident. You don't need to overthink it."
"Um... if you really feel that bad about it..."
"How about you treat me to a meal then?"
"I'm actually hungry...
But first, let me go grab my meds."
"My dad's calling."
"Aren't you gonna answer it?"
"Won't he get mad?"
"Yeah, he probably will."
"But... I'm really not ready to talk right now."
"Why?
Are you guys having issues?"
"Come on... He's your dad. He'll listen to you no matter what."
"I'm sure you guys can talk it out."
"Hey... or are you stressed about the competition?"
"Don't stress too much..
We still have another round left."
"Either way, I'm sure we'll win the next round."
"Hello? ...
Yes, P'Ya."
"What?!"
"How is P'Din doing?"
"Phew... Okay, got it."
"I'll go check on P'Din myself."
"Alright... Thank you so much, P'Yaa."